nicedeal.sg 2011-12-04

# Privacy | Singapore Group Buying - NiceDeal.SG nice way to save - Great Deals Daily!

**Privacy Policy**

Last Updated July 7, 2011

NiceDealPte. Ltd. or “NiceDeal.sg”, the provider of the Website (referred to as "us" or "we"),is firmly committed to protecting the privacy of our users. Our goal is to provide you with a secure online experience and to ensure that any information you submit to us is private and used/disclosed only for the purposes and in the means described below. This Privacy Policy discloses the privacy practices for the NiceDeal.sg websites (collectively, the "Website"). Please read the following to learn what information we collect from you (the "User" or the "End User") and how we use that information.   

If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please email us at _Support@nicedeal.sg_

PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY. BY ACCESSING OR USING OUR WEBSITE, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ, UNDERSTAND, AND AGREE TO BE BOUND TO ALL THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICYAND OUR WEBSITE TERMS OF USE. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THESE TERMS, EXIT THIS PAGE AND DO NOT ACCESS OR USE THE WEBSITE.

 **1\. Changes to Privacy Policy**

NiceDeal.sg will continue to commit itself to protecting and maximizing our users' privacy. We may change this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the revised Privacy Policy in the"Privacy Policy" section of the Website, it is the responsibility of each User to review the Website and the Privacy Policy periodically to learn of any revisions to this Privacy Policy. The revised Privacy Policy is effective immediately when posted on the Website. Your continued use of the Website after the effectiveness of such revisions will constitute your acknowledgment and acceptance of the terms of the revised Privacy Policy.

 **2\. Types of Information Collected and Uses of Collected Information**

We collect two types of information about our Website Users: Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information.

 **Personally Identifiable Information.** Personally Identifiable Information is information thatidentifies a specific End User. When you engage in certain activities on the Website, such as creating an account, filling out a survey, ordering a productor service from us, posting a review, sending us feedback, requestinginformation about our services, or applying for a job through the Website (collectively,"Identification Activities"), we may ask you to provide certaininformation about yourself. It is optional for you to engage in anIdentification Activity. If you elect to engage in an Identification Activity,however, we may ask you to provide us with certain personal information aboutyourself, such as your first and last name, mailing address, email address,telephone number and date of birth. When you order products or services, we mayalso ask you to provide us with your credit card number, expiration date andauthentication codes or related information. Depending on the activity, some ofthe information we ask you to provide is identified as mandatory and some isidentified as voluntary. If you do not provide the mandatory information for aparticular activity that requires it, you will not be permitted to engage inthat activity.

We use Personally IdentifiableInformation to provide products and services to you, enhance the operation ofthe Website, administer contests, improve our marketing and promotionalefforts, analyze Website use, improve our product and service offerings, and totailor your experience with third parties as provided in Item 3 of this PrivacyPolicy. For example, if you send our customer service an email we may use yourcomments and feedback to tell others about our services, and may post yourcomment in our marketing materials or on our Website. In addition, if you useour Website to send information or a product to another person, we may storeyour personal information, and the personal information of any recipient. Wemay use that other person’s contact information to allow him or her to view andaccept your gift or to allow the recipient to access the information yourequested we send. We may also use Personally Identifiable Information totroubleshoot, resolve disputes, accomplish administrative tasks, contact you,enforce our agreements with you, including our Website Terms of Use and thisPrivacy Policy, comply with applicable law, and cooperate with law enforcementactivities.

 **Non-Personally IdentifiableInformation.** Non-Personally IdentifiableInformation is information that does not identify a specific End User. Thistype of information may include things like the Uniform Resource Locator("URL") of the website you visited before coming to our Website, theURL of the website you visit after leaving our Website, the type of browser youare using and your Internet Protocol ("IP") address. We, and/or ourauthorized Third Party Service Providers and Advertisers, may automaticallycollect this information when you visit our Website through the use ofelectronic tools like Cookies and Web beacons or Pixel tags, as described inItems 4 and 8 of this Privacy Policy.

We use Non-Personally IdentifiableInformation to troubleshoot, administer the Website, analyze trends, gatherdemographic information, comply with applicable law, and cooperate with lawenforcement activities. We may also share this information with our authorizedThird Party Service Providers and Advertisers to measure the overalleffectiveness of our online advertising, content, and programming.

 **3\. Release of Personally Identifiable Information**

We will not share your Personally Identifiable Information with other parties except as provided below:

 **We may share your information with NiceDeal.sg Merchants.** From time to time, we provide offers from particular merchants (referred to as“NiceDeal.sg Merchants”) who, aspart of the offer, request information on NiceDeal.sg customers who purchasedthe offer. In those cases, we share some of your Personally IdentifiableInformation with NiceDeal.sg Merchants. Sharing this Information will allow a NiceDeal.sgMerchant to market directly to you should they choose to do so. However, wewill only share Personally Identifiable Information with a NiceDeal.sg Merchantif you engage in an Identification Activity, and then only to the NiceDeal.sgMerchant involved in that Identification Activity. Please note that we willonly provide a NiceDeal.sg Merchant your information with an opt-in notice toyou, in which you will have a chance to choose that NiceDeal.sg not give the NiceDeal.sgMerchant your personal information. We specifically disclaim any responsibility or liability for the actions of such NiceDeal.sg Merchant. While we inform themthat they are only permitted to communicate with you for the purposes of thespecific promotion with NiceDeal.sg, we do not have any responsibility for the actions of the NiceDeal.sg Merchant, and the actions of the NiceDeal.sg Merchantare not in our control.

 **We may share your information withAuthorized Third Party Service Providers.** We provide some of our services and products through third parties. These"Third Party Service Providers" perform functions on our behalf, likesending out and distributing our administrative and promotional emails. We mayshare your Personally Identifiable Information with such Service Providers tosend postal or email, remove repetitive information on customer lists, analyzedata, provide marketing assistance, provide search results and links, operatethe Website, troubleshoot, and provide customer service. We may also collectpersonal information from individuals and companies ("Affiliates")with whom we have business relationships and may have to also share theirinformation with Service Providers to accomplish our administrative tasks. Weencourage Third Party Service Providers to adopt and post privacy policies.However, the use of your Personally Identifiable Information by such parties isgoverned by the privacy policies of such parties and is not subject to ourcontrol.

 **We may share your information in aBusiness Transfer.** As with any other business, wecould merge with, or be acquired by another company. If this occurs, the successorcompany would acquire the information we maintain, including PersonallyIdentifiable Information. However, Personally Identifiable Information wouldremain subject to this Privacy Policy.

 **We may share your information forour Protection and the Protection of Others.** We may also disclose Personally Identifiable Information when we believerelease is appropriate to comply with the law or a court order; enforce orapply this Privacy Policy, our Website Terms of Use or other agreements; orprotect the rights, property or safety of the Website, its Users or others.

 **4\. Release of Non-PersonallyIdentifiable Information**

We may disclose or shareNon-Personally Identifiable Information with Partners, Affiliates andAdvertisers. For example, we may share aggregated demographic information(which does not include any Personally Identifiable Information) with"Third Party Advertisers" or "Third Party AdvertisingCompanies" and other parties as provided below:

We use Third Party AdvertisingCompanies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may useNon-Personally Identifiable Information about your visits to this and otherwebsites in order to provide, through the use of network tags, advertisementsabout goods and services that may be of interest to you.

We also use Third Party ServiceProviders to track and analyze Non-Personally Identifiable usage and volumestatistical information from our Users to administer our Website and constantlyimprove its quality. We may also publish this information for promotionalpurposes or as a representative audience for Advertisers. Please note that thisis not Personally Identifiable Information, only general summaries of theactivities of our Users. Such data is collected on our behalf, and is owned andused by us.

 **5\. Updating and CorrectingInformation**

We believe that you should have theability to access and edit the Personally Identifiable Information you provideus. You may change any of your Personally Identifiable Information by sendingus an email at support@nicedeal.sg. Please indicate your name and emailaddress, and what information you would like to update when you contact us.

We encourage you to promptly updateyour Personally Identifiable Information if it changes. In addition, in may beimpossible for us to completely delete all of your information because weperiodically backup information.

 **6\. User Choices on Collection andUse of Information**

As discussed above, you can alwayschoose not to provide information, although it may be required to engage in acertain activity on the Website. As a condition of purchase of our products andservices, we will send you Administrative and Promotional emails. We will sendyou information regarding your account activity and purchases as well asupdates about our products and promotional offers.

You cannot opt-out of AdministrativeEmails. "Administrative Emails" relate to a User's activity on theWebsite, and include emails regarding a particular User's account and requestsor inquiries. In contrast to Administrative Emails, however, you do have achoice with respect to Promotional Emails. Promotional Emails advertise ourproducts and services, and/or the products and services of our Advertisers and Affiliates. If you do not want to receive Promotional Emails from us, you mayelect to opt-out of receiving Promotional Emails at any time after registeringby e-mailing us at support@nicedeal.sg, or by hitting the"unsubscribe" button at the bottom of any of our e-mails. Whencontacting us, please indicate your name and email address, and whatPromotional Emails you do not want to receive.

 **7\. Security of Information**

We take security seriously and takenumerous precautions to protect the security of Personally Identifiable Information. You can access your Personally Identifiable Information on ourWebsite through a password and your email address. This password is encrypted.We recommend that you do not share your password with anyone. Any PersonallyIdentifiable Information resides on a secure server that only selectedpersonnel and contractors have access to. We encrypt certain sensitiveinformation using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology to ensure that yourPersonally Identifiable Information is safe as it is transmitted to us.

Unfortunately, no data transmission overthe Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As aresult, while we employ commercially reasonable security measures to protectdata and seek to partner with companies which do the same, we cannot guaranteethe security of any information transmitted to or from the Website, and are notresponsible for the actions of any third parties that may receive any suchinformation.

 **8\. Data Tracking**

 **Cookies.** To facilitate and customize your experience with theWebsite, we store cookies on your computer. A cookie is a small text file thatis stored on a User's computer for record-keeping purposes which containsinformation about that User. We use cookies to save you time while using theWebsite, remind us who you are, and track and target User interests in order toprovide a customized experience. Cookies also allow us to collectNon-Personally Identifiable Information from you, like which pages you visitedand what links you clicked on. Use of this information helps us to create amore user-friendly experience for all visitors. In addition, we may use ThirdParty Advertising Companies to display advertisements on our Website. As partof their service, they may place separate cookies on your computer. We have noaccess to or control over these cookies. This Privacy Policy covers the use ofcookies by our Website only and does not cover the use of cookies by anyAdvertiser. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you may be able tomodify your browser settings to decline cookies. Please note that if youdecline or delete these cookies, some parts of the Website may not workproperly.

 **Other Tracking Devices.** We may use other industry standard technologies like pixeltags and web beacons to track your use of our Website pages and promotions, orwe may allow our Third Party Service Providers to use these devices on ourbehalf. Pixel tags and web beacons are tiny graphic images placed on certainpages on our Website, or in our emails that allow us to determine whether youhave performed a specific action. When you access these pages or open or clickan email, pixel tags and web beacons generate a Non-Personally Identifiablenotice of that action. Pixel tags allow us to measure and improve ourunderstanding of visitor traffic and behavior on our Website, as well as giveus a way to measure our promotions and performance. We may also utilize pixeltags and web beacons provided by our Affiliates and/or Marketing Partners forthe same purposes.

 **9\. Privacy Policies of Third PartyWebsites**

This Privacy Policy only addressesthe use and disclosure of information we collect from you. Other websites thatmay be accessible through this Website have their own privacy policies and datacollection, use and disclosure practices. If you link to any such website, weurge you review the website's privacy policy. We are not responsible for thepolicies or practices of third parties.

 **10\. Miscellaneous Privacy Issues**

 **Children.** Minors under the age of 13 may not use the Website. We donot collect or maintain information from anyone known to be under the age of 13, and no part of the Website is designed to attract anyone under the age of18. NiceDeal.sg does not sell products for purchase by children. In certaininstances, we sell children's products for purchase by adults. If you are under 13, you may use NiceDeal.sg only with the involvement of a parent or guardian.

 **Public Areas.** We may provide areas on our Website where you can publiclypost information about yourself, can communicate with others, or can reviewproducts, restaurants, and submit media content. This information may beaccessible by other consumers and companies and may appear on other websites orweb searches, and therefore this information could be read, collected, and usedby others. For example, if you post your email address along with a publicrestaurant review, you may receive unsolicited messages. We have no controlover who reads your postings or what other users may do with the informationyou voluntarily post, so please use caution when posting any personalinformation.

All Inquiries | Support@nicedeal.sg
